http://www.westminstervillage.com/copyright-disclaimer-privacy-policy/

317.823.6841AboutContinuum of CareOur HistoryMissionLeadershipBoard of DirectorsWestminster FoundationResourcesResourcesEmploymentIn the MediaUpcoming EventsBlogEmploymentContact UsCopyright Disclaimer & Privacy PolicyAll materials posted on this site are subject to copyrights owned by Westminster Village North or other individuals or entities. Any reproduction, retransmission, or republication of all or part of any document found on this site is expressly prohibited, unless Westminster Village North or the copyright owner of the material has expressly granted its prior written consent to so reproduce, retransmit or republish the material. All other rights reserved.The names, trademarks, service marks and logos of Westminster Village North appearing on this site may not be used in any advertising or publicity, or otherwise to indicate the organization’s sponsorship of or affiliation with any product or service, with the organization’s prior express written permission.Although this website features links to other sites, Westminster Village North takes no responsibility for the content or information contained on those sites, as we do not exercise editorial or other control over these sites.This website provides information and services in furtherance of our mission. We make no representations about the suitability or accuracy of the information on this site for any purpose.If you see any objectionable, inaccurate or improperly functioning content or features on this site, please contact Director of Resident and Community Relations at (317) 823-6841, extension 2140, as soon as possible.Our Privacy PolicyWestminster Village North respects the privacy of visitors to its website. We strongly believe if electronic commerce and online activities are to flourish consumers must be assured that information provided online is used responsibly and appropriately. To protect online privacy, the organization has implemented the following policy.About the Information We CollectMost of the data and information we collect through our website is used only to help us achieve our mission. It is our policy to collect and store only personal information that our clients knowingly provide.From Casual Website Visitors and General Users.We do not collect any personal information from users browsing our website. When you use the public areas of our website you are doing so anonymously. We do collect aggregate use information, such as the number of hits (visits) per page. We use aggregate data for internal and marketing purposes, but we do not collect any personally identifying information.From Our Clients, Donors and Other Customers.If while visiting our website you order a product, register for a conference, submit a technical assistance question, or request other information, you will be asked to provide certain information. In all cases this information is submitted voluntarily. In most cases, we ask clients to provide their name, title, organization name, address, telephone, and e-mail. If you’re making a purchase, you may be asked for credit card information in order to complete your purchase. Similar information may be submitted to us on an order form or registration form.Customer ListsOur resident list is not for sale. When you visit our website or become a resident or make an inquiry, your name and mailing information will not be sold to any commercial organization.Credit Card Account InformationWe will utilize secure transaction methods when collecting credit card information over the Internet. Westminster Village North does not disclose credit card account information provided by our residents. We submit the information to the appropriate clearinghouse in order to obtain payment.How We Use CookiesCookies are small text files that are sent to your computer when you logon to a website that allow us to identify you when you return to the site. Westminster Village North uses cookies only to support the operations of our shopping cart. We do not use cookies to track your usage or any other personal information about you.
11050 Presbyterian Dr. Indianapolis, IN 46236 317.823.6841ResourcesIndependent LivingAssisted LivingHealth CenterConnect With UsRequest More InformationSchedule a TourContact UsWestminster Village North is a smoke-free campus.HIPAA Privacy Notice | Copyright Disclaimer & Policy | © 2019 by Westminster Village North
×Ready to Schedule a Tour?If you're ready to schedule a tour, please fill out the form below and we'll follow up to confirm your tour!Full Name*
First
Last Email* PhoneI am interested in:*Independent LivingAssisted LivingHealth CenterMemory CareOther - Please specify, below.What time during the day works best?
Morning
AfternoonIs there a day of the week that works better? (Select all applicable)
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
FridayMessagePlease note, someone from our team will contact you to confirm your your tour time and date once you submit this form.
×To close, click the "X" in the top right corner or tap "Escape" on your keyboard.
×Contact us If you would like to contact us, please fill out the form below.Full Name*
First
Last Email* PhoneI would like to:*I would like to...Receive additional informationSchedule a call to learn moreSchedule a tourLearn about employment opportunitiesI'm interested in:(Select all applicable)
Independent Living
Assisted Living
Skilled Nursing/Health Center
Memory CareI would like to receive information on...Independent LivingAssisted LivingSkilled Nursing/Health CenterMemory CareOther - Please specify, below.To learn more about employment opportunities with Westminster Village North, visit our Employment page.MessageCAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×Want to Schedule a Tour?If you're ready to schedule a tour, please fill out the form below and we'll follow up to confirm your tour!Full Name*
First
Last Email* PhoneWhich area(s) are you interested in?*(Select all applicable)
Independent Living
Assisted Living
Skilled Nursing/Health Center
Memory CareWhat time during the day works best?(Select all applicable)
Morning
AfternoonIs there a day of the week that works better?(Select all applicable)
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
FridayMessagePlease note, someone from our team will contact you to schedule a date and time for your tour.CAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×Want to Request More Information? If you're ready to request more information, fill out the form below and we'll contact you shortly!Full Name*
First
Last Email* PhoneI would like to:*I would like to...Receive additional informationSchedule a call to learn moreI am interested in:Independent LivingAssisted LivingSkilled Nursing/Health CenterMemory CareOther - Please specify, below.What time during the day works best?
Morning
Afternoon
EveningMessageCAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
